{
    "subject": "resource/Sumeet_Raghavan",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Mumbai",
    "human_readable": "Sumeet Raghavan was born in Mumbai.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9870498776435852,
            "question": "Is Mumbai the birthplace of Sumeet Raghavan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9250154495239258,
            "question": "Where was Sumeet Raghavan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8379157185554504,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Sumeet Raghavan was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7369328737258911,
            "question": "What city is associated with Sumeet Raghavan's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7193105220794678,
            "question": "To which city does Sumeet Raghavan owe his birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7016346454620361,
            "question": "What is the connection between Mumbai and Sumeet Raghavan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6470494866371155,
            "question": "If someone were to ask about Sumeet Raghavan's birthplace, what would you say?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5737304091453552,
            "question": "In which Indian city did Sumeet Raghavan come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5496014952659607,
            "question": "Can you tell me Sumeet Raghavan's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47050800919532776,
            "question": "Where did Sumeet Raghavan spend his early years?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sumeet Raghavan was born in Mumbai.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8499_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Sumeet Raghavan's place of origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8499_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which Indian city did Sumeet Raghavan come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8499_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone were to ask about Sumeet Raghavan's birthplace, what would you say?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8499_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8499_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8499_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8499_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8499_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8499_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8499_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8499_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8499_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8499_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8499_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the context information, there are multiple documents that mention Sumeet Raghavan's birthplace as Mumbai. For example, document 31.txt and document 67.txt both state that Sumeet Raghavan was born in Mumbai. This information supports the triple \"Sumeet Raghavan was born in Mumbai\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the provided documents, which consistently state that Sumeet Raghavan was born in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}